ZOSIMO UY, JR.

Computer Engineer



Oeneral Trias, Cavite









Summary

Diverse individual with knowledge in different technologies and over 4 years of experience technical troubleshooting, hardware, software and customer care. Knowledgeable in multiple programming languages, web-development, software development fundamentals and database management systems. Strong problem-solving skills and ability to adapt and work effectively in a team-based environment.

Work Experience

Conduent Philippines

Technical Advisor L2 · September 2019 - January 2023

- Provided L1 L2 support to customers of one Tech Giant in the US.
- Troubleshoot and resolves hardware, software defects and issues.
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to identify and prioritize resolution and requirements.
- Quickly adapt to new technologies and technical products.
- Maintained meets and exceeds KPI over the years of tenure.

Castem Philippines

Design Engineer · August 2018- January 2019

- Designed 3D injection molding and parts using SPACE-E/CAD
- Conducted design review and collaborate with other cross functional team.
- Developed programs for tooling and cutting using Space-E/CAM
- Quickly adapt to foreign technologies known as Space-E/CAD-CAM

Education

Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

System Technology Institute · 2012-2018

Certifications

Full-Stack Web Development Kodego Philippines · Feb-May (2023) **Developer Fundamentals**

SkillSoft June · 2023

Skills

Soft Skills

- Strong problem-solving
- Analytical skills
- Interpersonal Skills
- Communication
- Collaboration
- Leadership
- · Critical thinking

MySQL

Attention to detail

• Database Management

Hard Skills

- Web DevelopmentHTML, CSS, Javascript
- Software Design and Development Fundamentals
- Front-end Development
 React IS
- Local Environment & IDELaragon, VS Code
- Back-end Development
 Nedo is DUD Larayol
 - Node.js, PHP, Laravel
- Version ControlGit (Github)

Projects completed

Soulshine Web Final Capstone · 2023

Github repository: <u>Soulshine Beach</u>

Automated Bottle Washing Machine

Design Project - Thesis 2 · 2018

References: Available upon request.